<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Future Imperfect Slim</title>
    <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo Future Imperfect Slim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://natureinparadise.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Film Projects</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/multimedia/various_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/multimedia/various_projects/</guid>
      <description>Smithsonian Sleepover: thank you to volunteers  Scaling Ice: Climbing with the Dartmouth Mountaineering Club  Good Vibes &amp;amp; Duct Tape  Good Vibes &amp;amp; Duct Tape: Stories with Cindy Pierce from Dartmouth Film &amp;amp; Media Studies on Vimeo.
The Making of Good Vibes &amp;amp; Duct Tape  The Making of &amp;quot;Good Vibes &amp;amp; Duct Tape&amp;quot; from Dartmouth Film &amp;amp; Media Studies on Vimeo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Tips for your GRFP doctors DON&#39;T want you to know</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/grfp-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/grfp-advice/</guid>
      <description>These views, although informed by reading lots of other applications and conversations with other researchers, are my own. And it cannot be overstated that applying for the GRF is playing crapshoot: there is no sure way of winning, and the gamble is mostly luck. I felt motivated to write on this topic not because I consider myself an expert of this proposal, but in hopes that perhaps something that I learned through this process can pay off for someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Carbon Network covered in Smithsonian Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_publicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_publicity/</guid>
      <description>Our work on quantifying flux of carbon stocks in coastal wetlands was featured in the Smithsonian Environmental Research Center&amp;rsquo;s newsletter On the Edge.
Check it out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help restore the Amazon</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/multimedia/intern_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/multimedia/intern_video/</guid>
      <description>Check out the video I put together on the Alliance for a Sustainable Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Research Internship Program. A very cool experience! Learn more at www.sustainableamazon.org.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaching out: the importance of Outreach</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/reaching_out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/reaching_out/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute!  That&amp;rsquo;s in part because I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty preoccupied with applying for grad school, but also because I&amp;rsquo;ve taken my writing over toMongabay,&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;site&amp;nbsp;dedicated&amp;nbsp;to&amp;nbsp;environmental&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;conservation&amp;nbsp;news. Here&amp;rsquo;s some of my stories ; I especially enjoyed writing the piece on 3D printing reefs, which involved some fascinating conversations with a few individuals at the cutting edge of novel conservation work. Check them out!
Past that, this will be a quick post to share some thoughts on making an impact through your science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking flight</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/conservation_drones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/blog/conservation_drones/</guid>
      <description>When you think about conservation, what do you picture? Scientists collecting data in the mud or among the trees? Working with local landowners? Rearing the young of endangered species? While fieldwork is certainly critical, a surprising amount of science is conducted away from the field. The Smithsonian Conservation Biology Institute (SCBI) GIS lab is heavily involved in remote sensing – that is, collecting data without direct observation. One current project records changes in forest cover in Myanmar (formerly Burma).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/about/past_locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/about/past_locations/</guid>
      <description>PAST LOCATIONS:
Smithsonian Conservation Biology Institute, Front Royal, VA.
Madre de Dios, Peru.
LUMCON, Cocodrie, LA
One of the Gulf&amp;rsquo;s premiere research stations founded in 1979 Partnerships with Tulane, LSU, Nicholls U, and other schools Elevation in 2016: 3 ft above sea level Elevation in 2026: 5 ft below sea level
Little Cayman, BWI
one of the three Cayman Islands world-renowned for diving total permanent residential population: 17 beach: check.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>