<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>In_the_news on NATURE.IN.PARADISE</title>
    <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in In_the_news on NATURE.IN.PARADISE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research featured in the Centre ValBio annual report</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/cvb_annual_report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/cvb_annual_report/</guid>
      <description>The Madagascar research of our lab was featured in the annual report of Centre ValBio (CVB), Madagascar&amp;rsquo;s premiere research station. Check it out here!
Learn more about the CVB field stations here. We&amp;rsquo;ve done lots of our research here, and will continue to do so in the coming years&amp;hellip;.even if our next field season in Madagascar may be delayed just a tad due to the &amp;lsquo;rona outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching Campaign to Support Madagascar Climate Research</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/crowdfunder_announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/crowdfunder_announcement/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce that we are launching a crowdfunding campaign &amp;lt;/font to support our field research in Madagascar! Our work involves monitoring the microclimate of forested systems, in order to better understand what forest climate is relative to open-air temperatures (which is what weather towers measure), and how much forest climate will change into the future.
We&amp;rsquo;ve made great progress on the campaign so far, raising $3,570 so far in less than a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCN collaborators push to get Blue Carbon Bill introduced in the House of Representatives</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_bill/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the hard work of the Coastal Carbon Network and collaborators, a bill has been introduced in the US House of Representatives that would fund further efforts to advance blue carbon science (like the Coastal Carbon Network). Exciting to see where this goes!
The bill was introduced by Representative Bonamici of Oregon.
Check out the bill here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave Klinges joining NERC &#39;Constructing a Digital Environment&#39; Expert Network</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/nerc_expert_network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/nerc_expert_network/</guid>
      <description>Dave will be joining a Network of 28 international experts that will be providing diverse perspectives on improving the data journey of research and its application to policy and management. Very excited for this initiative!
Read more about the Digital Environment Expert Network here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coastal Carbon Network covered in Smithsonian Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_publicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://natureinparadise.github.io/in_the_news/ccrcn_publicity/</guid>
      <description>Our work on quantifying flux of carbon stocks in coastal wetlands was featured in the Smithsonian Environmental Research Center&amp;rsquo;s newsletter On the Edge.
Check it out here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>